Visit turkision.com for more!
Alps, stop.
Drop your swords.
You can not leave here alive.
Osman Bey.
Welcome, Osman Bey.
I was waiting for you.
I know men like you.
That is why I was sure you would come here.
I told you to drop your swords.
What will we do, Konur Bey?
Will we surrender to these dogs?
I will never drop my sword.
Nokers, shoot on my command!
It seems our destiny is to
be martyrs together, brothers.
However, I won't fall..
..before taking couple of these out.
You know why I am here!
For Princess Maria. And,
of course, for Karacelasun.
First, give me what I own. So that we may discuss.
What about Elcim Hatun, whose
mother and father you killed?
Elcim.
Do you have Elcim Hatun?
Alps!
Bring Elcim Hatun.
What is it?
When you heard her name
and learned she is with us..
..you looked shocked.
You come to Osman Bey’s
palace without fear, however..
..you are afraid of a young girl?
Let go.
You liar. You are not Tajeddin Noyan.
Do you wish for your death, Hatun?
He is wasting our time.
He is not Tajeddin Noyan.
Alaeddin, arrest his dogs outside.
Come on.
Handle it without spilling blood.
Alps! Arrest the nokers!
Put these dogs to prison!
If something happens to my father..
..I will send the heads of
these dogs to Tajeddin Noyan.
Karacelasun got caught to lure you to me.
So you fell into my trap.
Nokers!
Stop!
Alps, drop your weapons.
-What are you saying, Konur Bey?
-Do as I say.
If they intended to kill, they
would've done so long ago.
Osman Bey is still inside. It
seems there is something else.
Drop your swords, come on.
I won't care for your nokers
and butcher you in half right here.
No, Osman Bey.
You won't do such a thing..
..as I haven't killed you yet.
Look here.
What is your intention?
I came here to make an agreement in peace.
However, if you intend to do otherwise..
..none of us will leave here alive.
So you have the heart to do this.
I have a great heart, Osman Bey.
To show you my good intentions..
..I allow the others to go outside.
So that we may talk alone.
you want to talk with me..
..first, Elcim Hatun's family will come here.
We will see if they’re alive
or not. Then we will talk.
I knew you would want this. So I brought them.
You may leave.
Come on.
Now I will hear you.
What I'm about to say will be in
favor of both Kayis and llhanids.
Father.
Aunt.
Father!
-Father!
-My Elcim!
Let go!
-Father!
-Hatun!
-Elcim.
-Father!
-My daughter!
-Let my father go!
Elcim Hatun!
Stay calm! Don't act with anger.
My mother is dead, my brother is dead.
How can you tell me not to be angry?
If you're afraid, stand back, son of Bey.
-Father!
-My daughter!
Hatun! Stop!
-Run, save yourself Elcim!
-My daughter, my Elcim!
I would stay at the hands of these dogs more..
..for you and for my tribe!
Why did you come my daughter?
I would've given my life if
needed! Why are you here?
How could I left you to your fate, father?
I am also not alone. Osman Bey is with me.
Did you say Osman Bey? Thank Allah.
These valiants, are they Osman Bey’s valiants?
They already fell to Tajeddin Noyan's trap!
Gunduz Bey.
My father Osman Bey, came
here considering all possibilities.
Do not worry. We will get you out of here.
You, do not know how much of a tyrant..
..how vindictive, how cunning..
..this Tajeddin Noyan is!
That is why I am like this! Now he will kill..
..Osman Bey and his followers
You will give what you have.
-You want the Princess.
-Not only that..
..you will hand Karacelasun over to me.
Since sent his niece here..
..then this must not be the real
issue. Tell me what it really is.
That is preparing for a great expedition.
How big is it now, to reach as far as to us?
It will be an expedition
with big treasures and fame.
Those who will participate
will double their fame..
..as well as their gold.
Tell me then.
Will they walk towards Memluks or to Golden Horde?
If you give your alps under our command..
..and act under us in this war..
..then you can learn.
Stop there.
Our alps only fight on Allah’s way.
It seems you and we do not share a common cause.
Know this well. I will not give..
..not a single alp under your command.
However, you did not hear
what you will have in return.
I will have my uncle..
..confirm that small personal beylik of yours..
..in return of a small tax cost.
Look here, a beylik that needs to be confirmed..
..is neither free nor personal.
You only look for a beylik to feed until it dies.
Then, know that you are in wrong lands!
We never bowed down to anyone.
A lot of blood has been spilled for that.
We will spill it if needed, know that well.
you insist on this..
..you will see the side of
me that you never saw before.
And every child..
..every woman in your land pays the price of that.
There is no need for that, Osman Bey.
Noker!
Everyone who came with
Osman Bey are free to leave!
Now tell me.
Where is Osman Bey?
Osman is Great Tajeddin Noyan's guest.
Bala Hatun.
Don't break the tradition of visiting anymore.
Now Osman Bey’s life...
...depends on Tajeddin Noyan's mercy.
Your life depends on our
mercy! You inglorious dastard
You drew us into a trap, huh?
Get him up.
You used Karacelasun as a bait against us.
You can't compete with Amir Tajeddin's mind.
Baysungur, send the alps
after Osman Bey immediately.
Don’t even try.
Nobody can get out of there alive as
long as Tajeddin Noyan doesn't want.
Your alps would be dead. Shahzade.
Put this dog in the dungeon.
Get off! Leave me.
You'll take this woman and your alps and leave.
Your Bey will come after you.
Alps! Let's go.
I'm not going anywhere without my father and aunt!
If Osman Bey didn't have a
plan, he wouldn’t let us go.
He should tell about this plan. Besides,
What did he talk to Tajeddin Noyan and he lets
us go? I'm not going anywhere without them!
Daughter, enough
You go with them!
-I can't leave you here like this, father.
Knowing you’re fine makes us feel well.
-Just go!
-Come on, come on.
-Come on, dear.
-Father.
Go with them. Don't do anything crazy.
Look. Look at me.
You heard your father.
I know you're worried about your father and aunt.
But you should know Osman
Bey must have planned everything.
Otherwise, he wouldn't let us go.
We'll save both your father
and aunt with Allah's will.
But we need to go now.
Come on, alps!
-Father!
-Daughter!
-Don't do anything crazy, dear.
-Elcim!
-My dear. Just go. dear! Go. Elcim
My dear...
If these are your terms,
If you intend to make me a bey under your
command and make my soldiers your soldiers,
...the IIkhanid State will perform
their first campaign on me then.
The conditions will be better.
Things will change. Do not hurry.
Just think about it.
It's not an easy matter.
I have time. Now..
Leave calmly and go back to your land.
Tajeddin Noya
I'm expecting to see you in my dinner table...
...in Yenisehir tomorrow.
Come and we'll discuss everything in details.
You understand me. Let me understand you then.
Don't worry. There won't be a trap.
I'll be there.
Stay safe, Osman Bey.
Stay safe.
Osman Bey... Praise be!
Gunduz Bey who became captive...
...to make his people free.
Isn't a Bey’s duty protecting
his people, Osman Bey?
Isn't our primary goal their freedom?
It is. Of course it is. May Allah
send more people like you.
Don't be worrying. You didn't bow against them.
I won't let these dogs hunt you.
Thank you, Osman Bey. Thank you.
My time is over.
I have a great suffering. You
know what my only solace is?
My daughter being safe with you.
She brought soldiers here with her.
They fight under your command now.
I know your suffering. Don't
worry. You will find better solace.
We’ll make them pay for this.
Look what I’m saying!
I'm telling a Turkish Bey to give up. Huh.
For sure, your soldiers will come.
Your Beys will line up before you.
Don't you lose your hopes.
Tell me. How did they make you fall?
We didn’t..
...let Olcaytu collect our alps.
But Tajeddin Noyan
...played different tricks and deceived us.
He made my deceased son
and me turn against each other.
I buried my son while we were at odds.
Osman Bey... We were at odds.
Then we got stuck between Konya and Tabriz.
They smashed us and we’ve ended up here.
Listen, Osman Bey. Don't hang out with this dog.
This dog...
..is a demon speaking with the right tongue.
And his tongue is even sharper than a dagger.
Nothing but killing would stop him.
But just like our escape,
...that's impossible.
You think I will leave..
...Hayme Mother’s children to these dogs?
Don't be worrying. By
either killing or stopping them,
...I will save you from this place.
Thank you.
I will crush Tajeddin Noyan
You brought me here for no
reason, Orhan Bey! I won't stop!
I won't stop! I will go back and take my father.
Hatun... Do as I say.
e will wait for my father's return.
Osman Bey won't be able to
stand against Tajeddin Noyan.
It's obvious. Let me go..
...and let me do it myself.
-Elcim Hatun!
I told you, we will wait for my father's return!
What happened, Orhan?
What is happening here?
Where is Osman Bey?
He is with Tajeddin Noyan. He
ordered us to come here before him.
He will tell you everything when he comes back.
That Tajeddin Noyan used
Karacelasun as a bait on purpose.
He was luring us into a game from the beginning.
What kind of a snake is that?
My father and my aunt are
still in the hands of that man!
How can I stay here?
-You will stay, my daughter.
Your patience will be your weapon.
Osman Bey will come, we
will understand the situation
and what is necessary
will be done for sure.
Come on.
After you, Elcim Hatun. Come on.
Nokers! Give some water to Gunduz Bey and Hatun.
They brought Kayis' Bey Osman to me.
We won't drink even a drop...
...of your water.
You will never be able to control Osman.
Do you understand? -Osman is a smart man.
Sooner or later, he will bow down to me.
If he doesn't...
...I will make him bow down.
You will see. This time...
...your plans will not work.
Tajeddin Noyan!
And then... I will cut your head off.
You couldn't become any wiser.
I killed people in your tribe, your Alps.
I killed your wife and your son.
I thought you would become wiser.
-I did!
I didi I will torture you until you die!
I am wiser now!
Let's assume that you
don't show mercy to yourself.
But don't you show mercy to
this Hatun, the entrustment...
..of your son
I am honored that my Bey
does not bow to dogs and jackals.
Take me out of here, and
I will show youi Open this!
Be patient. Soon, I will get what I want.
Then... you will also bow down.
Prepare my horse!
-My father...
-My daughter..
You are alright. You are alright, thanks to Allah.
I am alright, I am alright. Don't worry.
I was afraid something was
going to happen to you, father.
No... don't be afraid. Who can hurt me?
I never do something
before I make sure it is safe.
My Beyl Thanks to Allah, you are alright.
We are alright...
Thank Allah we are..
Now, the helper under the
guise of Tajeddin Noyan...
...where is that dog?
In the dungeon, my Bey.
What happened to Gunduz Bey
and his daughter in law Ayca Hatun?
Tajeddin Noyan does not want to give them to us.
He wants to take without giving.
Come on, I'll be waiting
for everyone at the council.
Tajeddin Noyan set his eyes on Osman.
Today he tested him, but if he does
not obey tomorrow, he will destroy them.
Tajeddin Noyan does not let
others notice him before he...
...gets his teeth into his prey.
And he knows it is difficult to attack Osman.
That dog must've set his game accordingly.
Osman Bey is the last chance of Kayis.
If he falls, Kayis will disappear.
No... Kayi will exist forever.
We will get out of this place in some way.
And we will stand before that dog like lions.
How many times have we tried, dad?
-Stop... I will not give up on
freeing myself from this captivity..
...and rescuing my tribe...
...and my daughter.
Being trapped here like this...
..hurts me.
I will either confront that dog...
...and kill him...
...or die with honor.
But not like this.
Not like this.
Olcaytu Khan is getting ready
for a war. He wants Alps from us.
But his real intention is to weaken our power.
They don't want anyone to get stronger...
...in these lands after the Seljuks.
They will lead us into a war and feed the
Byzantines with us at our weakest moment.
Of course, if we bow down.
Gunduz Bey did not bow down.
That's why they started by attacking his tribe.
So, what path do you think
we should follow, my Bey?
Tajeddiri Noyan
...hides his iron fist...
...behind a velvet glove.
I have invited him to my table to gain time.
Why are you trying to gain time, Osman Bey?
For the great war I will start.
Now...
...send news to all the Beys, to all the tribes.
We are entering a new war.
Let them know that this war is very important...
...for the future of the Turks.
But before that...
...we will go to Tajeddin Noyan's headquarters
to take Gunduz Bey and Ayca Hatun.
They are from Kayi tribe...
...and Hayme mother's lineage.
They are our grace and honour.
If we let them take someone
from us, how will others trust us?
How are we going to take my
father and my aunt from them?
I placed Turahan at the
headquarters of Tajeddin Noyan...
...as a spy when we went there.
My Bey... Is it enough for
us to have a spy inside?
How will we carry out the attack there?
That place is Tajeddin
Noyan's captive headquarters.
He brought him there to show that he was alive...
But he will take them to his actual headquarters.
It will be enough for us if our spy Turahan
informs us about this, right, my Bey?
Are we going to save them on the way?
Taking your family from him will not weaken...
...his power.
He will surely demand a dog from these lands.
He will want to take whoever...
..hates us the most.
He will talk to Mehmet Bey, my Bey.
And he will celebrate it, my Bey. He has
been trying to attack us for a long time.
He can't do anything.
Since I placed Cerkutay by his side...
...I have been controlling his leash.
Move, you mani Why are you
standing in the middle of the way?
Don't you hear us?
I am talking to you!
Move!
A man who dares to confront me like this...
...must be counting on something.
Tell me. Who are you?
You are the famous Executioner of Byzantine, huh?
Turcopole?
Imren Tegin.
As he forgave the trouble-maker...
...who worked with Templars and raided Thrace,
...Andronikos must be so desperate.
He sent me...
...because he didn't want you
to stay helpless against Osman...
...after Geyhatu, Nayman and Gorklu Khan.
We trust the help of the helpless, Imren Tegin.
What did your emperor promise you?
I will own the castles in the
border in return for Osman's head.
What if I don’t want Osman's head?
You don’t want Osman's head
Tell me then. You want him to take your head?
I have no intention to
destroy Osman or Kayi people.
Are you planning to take Turks under your command?
You don't know us, Tajeddin
Noyan. Don't forget this.
I'm a Turk too. Turks will never obey you.
Like I didn't obey the emperor.
Do you know how to tame a
pack of wolves, Imren Tegin?
If you put wolves in a cage,
...they never obey you.
You need to tame them in their natural habitat.
Without scaring, without annoying.
Slowly.
Will you send the wolves you turn
into dogs against your enemies?
Your Sultan Olcaytu is seeing a dream.
What if the pack gather
and cause a trouble for you?
As long as we don't want,
...nobody can cause a trouble
for anybody, Imren Tegin.
If they disobey the high order,
...then I will take Osman’s head.
You think you can take Osman’s head on your own?
My Bey.
What about the princess?
How long will we keep her here?
Princess..
It's time for Princess now. She'll
be captured by Tajeddin Noyan.
And she'll bring information
from there as our spy.
And we will keep our promise.
Osman Bey.
You're talking about your
plans. The princess, a spy...
You say you'll save my family.
It's okay so far...
But you never mention
Tajeddin Noyan's lifeless head!
Girl.
I know you're furious.
But you can't act with ambition during a fight.
We're trying to act in the right way.
-Osman Bey!
-Elcim Hatuni
You're in Osman Bey's presence. Know your place.
We're struggling for your
and your family's health.
Malhun.
We did everything that we can do with minds.
The rest is up to courage and strength.
Send messages to all the
beysj I’m declaring mobilization.
We'll either vanish or as a great state,
...we'll get rid of this trouble.
You yourself should wrap your own wounds.
Nobody can help you.
Elcim, are you available?
I didn't realize because of the hunting clothes.
But you are so beautiful. Praise be.
Thanks.
"Your fate should be beautiful
first", my mother used to say.
Malhun Hatun, I couldn't save my father and tribe.
I can do nothing.
Obviously, Osman Bey isn't on our side either.
You don't know Osman Bey, dear.
Osman Bey never lets anybody down.
He'll save your father,
sister-in-law and other people.
Don't be worrying.
I don't know if you understand me, Malhun Hatun.
But I learned that I should trust nobody.
I have nobody but my father who I can count on.
I was like you when I came to these frontiers.
I didn't care about anything
else but my father and tribe,
...which means I understand you well.
I know why you dress like this and
that you feel that you have to stay strong.
You're a Bey's daughter.
You are supposed to protect your father's legacy.
But remember this.
You're not alone, dear. We're with you.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
One side of mine is angry with me.
You didn't believe me.
My other side...
...asks me what I would do if I
were you. It thinks you're right.
I wish this had never happened, Scholar.
Gonca, wait. We need to talk.
My father left us here not to let
Osman feel free in the frontiers.
-Your mind is still...
-I set my mind on my duty, brother.
-You mind your own business.
-Gonca.
I'm responsible for you while father is away.
Don't you meet that dog called Alaaddin.
Nobody appointed you as my watcher!
Both you and I will only perform our duties.
One of my duties is Alaaddin! Don't you meet him!
Otherwise, I will kill you with him.
You will kill, huh?
Fine. Kill then! Come on, do it! Kill me, brother!
-What are you waiting for? Just kill me!
-Stop, Gonca!
What are you doing?
Pull yourself together!
You can't kill someone who is already dead.
I'm dead. Have you forgotten
How could you forget,
brother? Everybody remembers.
How could you forget?
I'm Gonca, daughter of Yakup Bey.
Gonca the Spy! How could you forget?
-Pull yourself together!
Everybody remembers! You forgot?
Pull yourself together,
Gonca! Did you lose your mind?
May I come in, Mehmed Bey?
Come in, Cerkutay.
Tajeddin Noyan is here.
-Why is he here?
-I don’t know.
But we will see, Gonca.
Tajeddin Noyan never comes
for something good. Be cautious.
Let's start.
In the name of Allah, the merciful, the compassionate.
-Thank you, my Bey.
Ghazi, are you full? Why are not eating?
Are you thinking about your father?
Osman Bey, I was so happy
to come together with my father.
But we got separated again.
Boy, he's there for a duty.
Don't worry. He'll be back after the duty.
I'll gladly suffer the longing as
long as the homeland is safe.
Well..
Mother, you look so thoughtful. What's the matter?
If you're worried about Tajeddin Noyan,
...we will take care of
this too with Allah's will.
Do you have another problem, Mother Malhun?
My Bey.
I have things to say if you let me.
Of course, you can.
Sons, I've been having a dream for a long time.
What is it, mother?
I was in ihram in my dream.
I was on the way to Hajj.
My sons, I'll go to Hajj.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Welcome. You honor our tribe, Tajeddin Noyan.
I've Heard That Yakup Bey Want to Kutayha..
..and left the marketplace to his children.
This marketplace, in the end..
..is llhanids, it is mine.
I want to see how it is myself.
You've heard it correct.
Foal grows while horse rests.
Children grows, father rests.
My father left me and my sister here to grow it.
Is this the only thing that brought
you here uninvited, Tajeddin Noyan
You must be Gonca Hatun.
You are correct.
My only intention to come to
the marketplace is not only this.
If Yakup Bey is not here, his son is here.
I want to talk with him.
Alone.
Everyone leave.
You too, Gonca.
We are finally alone, Mehmed Bey.
The nephew of Grand Olcaytu.
-What does he want to talk with me?
-About your nemesis.
We will talk about Osman.
Mother, when will you
depart with Allah's permission?
Tomorrow morning, if Allah allows it, son.
Mother.
Why so quickly?
Let me come with you.
I can not do without you.
My dear daughter, you can not go anywhere.
You will stay here.
You will go where I go.
May Allah grant you safe travels, mother Malhun.
Give our regards to those blessed lands.
If Allah permits, my son.
I did not want to leave you
in these hard times, however..
.after seeing the same dream over and over.
Do not worry, Malhun.
We will look after this place.
Do not worry, mother. We are here.
Of course.
However, I still worry.
I thought about staying, however..
..the road awaits me.
Do not worry.
You will be beside us with prayers.
Safe travels, Malhun Hatun.
Since you have a long road ahead..
..you need a healer too, right?
Take Shahzade Alaeddin with you
Look here, do you want this
for Malhun Hatun or yourself?
Why would I want this for myself?
I want it for Malhun Hatun.
Also, a Shahzade would be good.
Right, my Bey? Shall he go?
-No.
Alaeddin has his own duty. He can not go anywhere.
However, you can.
No, I have a duty as well.
You already know. With your permission, my Bey.
Look at this one.
Mother. I will miss you so much.
My angel daughter. I will miss you too.
I will miss all of you.
It seems they won't do anything.
I will see to my own business.
I brought something to eat,
Elcim Hatun. Please enjoy.
Thank you. Put it there please.
Where are you going with your sword
in the middle of the night Elcim Hatun?
I had to do this.
Ahjger is the realest emotion
in’this world Mehmed Bey.
Anger is the realest emotion
in this-world Mehmed Bey.
Do you know why?
Because it can not be faked, like love.
However, not like respect.
The moment I mention Osman..
..I hear you grinding your teeth.
Say what you must, Tajeddin Noyan.
That is the real courage.
Talking, by preventing fear.
You are a valiant man,
Mehmed Bey. So is your father.
That is why you could not face Osman.
Because, he is no valiant.
Continue, Tajeddin Noyan
Yakup Bey, did not break
the hand he could not bend.
In the end, he had to shake it.
Because Osman..
..abused your father's good intention.
He misused it.
May Allah protect us from the likes of him.
You are different from your father.
You can break that hand.
Osman drags people to
disaster in disguise of dream.
Now he is preparing to face you.
On top of that, he made fool
of us around all these people.
I am not like my father. I will break that hand.
That is swell. We will soon..
..go on an expedition full of treasure and fame.
You will give me alps for this expedition.
My father won't allow this, Tajeddin Noyan.
At that very point..
..one must become a coward again, Mehmed.
One needs to remember.
One needs to remember why..
..their father left their
home and ran off to Kutahya.
One needs to realise who they're going against.
we haven't disagreed yet, Tajeddin Noyan.
That is your duty. Convince your father.
And I will back you up..
..on your fight against Osman.
On top of that, I can break that hand for you.
We are okay to the hand that needs breaking.
However, I have a question for you as well.
You will give me one answer.
Did you shoot that arrow..
..to my father?
Look,son.
This is my heraldry ring.
The moment I send this ring to Tabriz..
Every noker of llhanids come to my aid.
A hundred thousand, even two
hundred thousand, however...
..why would I just go..
.and plan assassination to the Bey of Kutahya?
Do not make me laught, Mehmed.
I asked a question and got my answer.
We will do great things with you, Mehmet.
Great things.
Elcim Hatun is running away, catch her!
She won't stay calm. Alp
Close the exits. Come on.
Hatun, stop
You are trying for no reason... For no reason.
What happened, Hatun? Where are you going, huh?
I am telling you to stop. Don't you hear me?
-Orhan Bey!
Tell me.
-Move!
-I will go and take my father.
-Give me patience, Allah!
Elcim Hatun.
I told you that you cannot go
anywhere. Go to your room now.
I can break all the walls if
necessary, and I will go there!
It's obvious... It's obvious..
You know how to break things.
You left me no other choice, Orhan Bey
-Sisters!
Take Elcim Hatun to her room.
Apparently, she lost her way.
Don't touch me! Let me go!
You cannot control me in a room!
Let me go!
Did the Lords who disgraced Byzantium arrive?
They did. They are talking about
the tax they will pay to Osman.
Weak men... Do we need enemies
when we have those weak men?
These dogs are carrying water
with a bucket to the mad river.
I will dry them up first...
...then that river.
Malhun... I know that you really want to go...
...but you won’t go to Hajj for now.
But everyone will think that
you are on the way to Hajj.
You will go to Turkmen Beys.
You will tell them to support me.
You will flare up the dying flame of Gaza.
When they see the mother
of the state before them...
...they will understand how serious it is.
As you say, my Bey... But
why am I going there secretly?
The army of great gaza
will be established secretly.
You won't put yourself in danger either.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
All preparations have been
completed to set out, my Bey.
Konur will come with you.
Konur. Malhun Hatun is entrusted directly to you.
You will visit all the Beys and tribes.
I will protect your entrustment with my life,
my Bey. Whoever’s heart beats with us...
...will stand by the protector
of the Turks, my Bey.
When you fulfill your duty
properly, neither Tajeddin Noyan...
...nor the executioner of the Romans
will be able to stand against us.
The path is clear, and those
who walk on it are known, my Bey.
The duty of the Hajj can wait for now.
First, I will fulfill my duty for the
glarification of the word of Allah.
Thank you.
We cannot be strong without a union.
We will first get strong..
...then we will be a state
which will rule the whole world.
May our gaza be blessed.
-If Allah permits my Bey.
If Allah permits, if Allah permits.
Collecting the taxes to be sent
to Osman has become difficult.
In the end, he seized the goods of the
merchants and people, causing unrest.
They are now unable to pay the taxes.
Then don't pay the taxes.
-How?
With which power, Olivia?
This gold prevents Osman from
reaching the walls of our castle, Olivia.
Cowards... Do you think this gold can stop Osman?
You only made him stronger.
Imren Tegin. The executioner of Roman Empire.
And you must be the sheep of Byzantium.
You have endured well with
these cowards until now, Olivia.
How can you come in like
this and talk to nobles this way?
What nobility? Aren't you the
Lords who surrendered to Osman?
If the Emperor supported us,
we wouldn't be obliged to this.
He cannot leave us alone
question us at the same time.
Is the Emperor in such a
helpless state to send you?
How much gold did you give Osman?
Who are you? I am not
going to answer to a Turcopole!
I would rather die.
-Is that so?
Your prayers are accepted
Are you with me, Olivia?
I am with whoever brings Osman's end.
Good. You are a smart woman.
You will manage the castles of
the deceased lords on my behalf.
Osman won't know anything.
Things will remain as they are.
With the order of the Emperor.
Do you know why I accepted this duty, Olivia?
Since you killed the Lords..
...since you took their castles
with the order of the Emperor...
...you want to be the only ruler here.
You are a smart woman.
Will you be able to do this alone?
You cannot even imagine what I can do alone.
But no one can imagine
what I can do when I have the..
...support of Tajeddin Noyan and his nokers.
Let me go
My Shahzade, I...
-Forgive us, Kismet Hatun.
Sisters... Take care of her.
Let me go, Orhan Bey! I
will go and save my father!
Elcim Hatuni
Don't you hear us?
No... I understood you.
You cannot help me. Get out of my way!
-What are you?
You seem smart one day,
you seem stupid the other day!
Who are you to call me stupid?
Isn't what you're doing stupidity?
Elcim Hatun...
Tajeddin is serious.
With the slightest mistake you make...
...he will behead your father and your aunt.
My family is dying anyway,
Orhan Bey! Your father...
...is going to make an agreement with that
dog, who killed my mother and my brother!
Hatun... You don’t know my father and..
...my family, Hatun.
You don't know us.
Yes. I don't know you or your father.
But I know Tajeddin Noyan very well.
If I don't make a move now, I
will lose my father and my aunt.
Understood... You won't pull yourself together.
Orhan Bey! What are you doing?
Orhan Bey, what are you
doing? Orhan Bey, open the door!
Orhan Bey
You left me no other choice,
Hatun. Have a good rest.
Orhan Beyl Open the door! Orhan Bey!
Have a good rest, so you
can pull yourself together. Alps.
This door will remain locked. The
Hatun inside will never come out.
Come on. I will make you pay for this Orhan Bey!
Come on.
-I will make you pay for this, Orhan Bey!
I will make you pay for this!
He says he will put a leash on a Turk...
...especially a stubborn Gokboru like Osman.
He will use him as a pawn in his own war.
They'll do politics. Stupid man.
If he's a stupid man, I'm the executioner.
Why did we come here?
For blood!
What are we going to die for?
For lands! For a war!
When war is necessary at a
place, doing politics means nothing.
Strong ones win in a war.
We will start this war and end it the way we want.
I set the rules of the game,
and if necessary, I break them.
Tajeddin Noyan might think
he is allies with Byzantium.
-What will be our move, Imren Tegin?
-We will attack Osman...
...from his weakest spot,
his family, his beloved ones.
e will bring him close to us step by step.
You will bring me the head of Alaeddin.
I will make him experience the
worst pain. I will take his son from him.
-I will send my most talented man.
-No.
Alaca will handle this.
Alaca. Sneak in the city.
Fulfill your duty quickly.
These lands and these castles belong to us now!
We don't take orders from anyone,
we don't pledge allegiance to anyone.
We start the games and wars, and we end them.
Let the swords be unsheathed now.
Even if we water these
lands with our blood, we
will not put our swords
back into their sheaths...
..until we make Osman kneel!
Long live Imren Tegin!
Malhun mother...
May Allah let you go there safely, I hope.
My valiant son... My Alaeddin... Thank you.
May Allah be with you.
-You too, mother, you too.
Mother...
-My Orhan...
My lion son..
You and your siblings are entrusted to each other.
You will always stay united, alright?
Your mother is always here.
Don't forget.
My mother... Don't worry about us, alright?
Nothing will change here until you come back.
We will always stay united.
May Allah be with you.
You top, my mother... You too.
My Fatma... My beautiful eyed, angel daughter...
Don't be sad...
I will go to Beytullah with Allah's consent.
I will put my face on the
sacred lands and come back.
We will not be away from each other forever.
I know... I know, my mother...
May you go there safely.
May you go quickly and come back quickly.
Amen, beauty. Amen.
Keep your eyes on your brothers.
And don't you disobey Mother Bala.
My strong daughter. May Allah protect you.
Malhun Hatun, have a safe journey.
Give me your pardon in this world
and Qiyamah if I ever offended you.
You have my pardon, Ulgen. You pardon me too.
You have my pardon.
Alps, give me your pardon
in this world and Qiyamah.
You have my pardon
You have my pardon too, but what
will you bring for me from Mecca?
Whatever you want, Ghazi Alp.
You’re going to stone the
devil. I want one of those stones.
A stone can repel the devil may
do even more to the heathens!
Alright, I will bring some.
Ghazi, those stones aren't anything like that.
But if you want, we can make a sword for you.
-You can fight the heathens with it.
-That will do, my Bey!
That's my boy. Konur.
-Is everything set?
-Everything is set, my Bey.
Alps to escort us are waiting
for us outside Yenisehir.
Let's go then.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
Do you know why Tajeddin
Noyan is here, Cerkutay Bey?
I don't know, Gonca Hatun. But he wouldn't
be here if he didn't seek something big.
Right. Right.
Gonca Hatun, are you waiting to see me off?
I wouldn't have kept you waiting if I had known?
No. You misjudged.
We have no traditions like seeing the
uninvited guests off, Tajeddin Noyan.
They can go just like they come.
Gonca Hatun, I can see that my being here...
...bothered you.
Your face looking like a rosebud...
...is spreading anger for me.
The poison in your heart is obvious in your face!
You can't hide it with your words.
I had a thing to do. But I caught you
here before you left, Tajeddin Noyan.
I like people who put the
duty above anything else.
I was so pleased with my time here.
I will come again soon.
But...
If you collaborate with Osman,
...I won't be your guest next time...
..but your death.
Well... Stay safe.
Stay safe.
Whoever denies his origin has no place among us.
Ashm beni inkar etti ise ne gelir elden?
..if my origin has denied me?
Mighty Amir.
Osman's wife is going to Hajj.
And Osman is on the way to see her off.
Bring that woman to me.
I can't pay a visit with empty hands.
Osman's wife. Let's catch her
-They're coming, my Bey.
-Alps.
Our target will be Gunduz Bey and Ayca Hatun.
Let's show them Turks cannot be imprisoned!
-As you order, my Bey!
-Let’s go! Giddap!
Come on!
Osman Bey!
Are you alright?
We are alright, thanks to you.
How did you find us in this
middle of nowhere, Osman Bey?
Osman put even his life in danger to rescue you.
Now, he will squirm to learn where you are.
I will make him my dog thanks to you.
No one will learn where these two will be!
Take them!
This Tajeddin.. First he drove a
wedge between me and my son..
..then he did the same with
Hatun. He drove a wedge between..
..Ayca Hatun and my son. He
played mind games to my son.
Then, he started carving us out from the inside.
He said "Gather all Beys to the same council."
His intention is to gather alps from them as well.
However, you can not put leash..
..on a Turk's neck.
Then, they attacked our tribe.
He put my mother and my Bey in a tent.
They burned it down, Osman Bey.
Some ran away, some fell.
They started destroying us
one way or another, Osman Bey.
They do not do an expedition..
..this is an expedition to destroy us.
Do not worry. I understand you well.
I understand you the most.
However..
..we have two roads ahead of us. Tell me..
..do you want to be free..
..or want to be safe?
We already picked our road, Osman Bey.
Our road is your road.
Thank you. We are still free, thank Allah.
We are still free.
However, know this..
We have a great war ahead of us.
They are well prepared.
Now, Olcaytu wants to begin.
However..
..if we can slow him down..
The harder we resist..
..the more Tajeddin Noyan..
..will be in a tight spot.
Not only he will fall in a tight spot..
..maybe he will lose his status as well.
I know, your tribe is broken.
However, if there is still a hope..
..it is because of you.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Even hearing this, cools my heart off.
Thank you.
Now, they want to scatter us.
However, now two Kayi unites.
They will not succeed.
-What will we do?
-The same thing we always do!
We will move towards them!
The only victor is Allah!
Allah is the greatest!
I heard your fiance is captive in Konya.
I will save your fiance and
make you two come together.
You will caught by Tajeddin Noyan...
...and be our spy.
I'm ready to do anything, Osman Bey.
Move.
Now what my Beys wants has happened.
Tajeddin... Noker!
I want to see your face
when you realize the truth.
Finally.
Ayca.
Sister-in-law.
Thanks to Allah, you're fine.
Don't, Ayca. The danger isn’t over yet.
Why? We're free now. Will we
keep the truth from Osman Bey?
Father.
-Shh.
She will be sister-in-law for some time, alright?
Nobody will know...
...Ayca and you changed places.
Things will be more complicated..
...if Osman Bey finds out, dear.
They will face the same trouble sooner or later.
We need to tell them.
I'm glad you are together again.
Elcim Hatun mentioned you a lot.
-Welcome again.
-Thank you.
-Gunduz Bey.
-Yes?
-Osman Bey expects you in the council.
-Is that so?
Alright. I should go then, Bala Hatun.
Sure.
Thank you, Bala Hatun. Our family
are back together thanks to you.
Thanks. We will never forget
about this favor for yours, Bala Hatun.
We did our part, dear.
Your captivity is over, Ayca Hatun.
We’ll take care of those dogs
all together. Don't be upset.
None of us can compete with him.
You don't know him, Bala Hatun.
Tajeddin is not like any other enemies.
He takes his strength from his
mind. It's impossible to beat him.
Impossible?
Obviously, he scared you.
This is not fear.
Tajeddin knows well how to play with his prey.
He never plans to kill his
enemy but do more than death.
He turns his enemies into slaves for himself.
TACETTTN NOYAN HEADQUARTERS
-Do I have permission?
-Come in.
Mighty Amir, we got Princess Maria.
They're bringing her to the tent.
Osman, now I got you.
Treat the woman kindly.
I will go see Osman and give him the great news.
Whywould you invite Tajeddin Noyan...
...to the dinner, Osman Bey?
He is the killer...
...of my wife, child and people.
I know, Gunduz Bey. I know that.
You don't know, Osman Bey. You don't.
If you intend to talk to him to make an agreement,
...you don't know.
Behind his naive face, there is a raving animal.
Even a dog hunts to fill its stomach.
But he kills for pleasure.
He chained all my soldiers to each other...
..and threw them into a fire pit.
He sat on the chair and watched them.
He also made me watch.
He's quite a monster, Osman Bey.
Quite a monster.
Tajeddin Noyan
...is like a wild flood.
If we stand like a deadwood against him,
...we will vanish away.
But we will be a plane tree
to stand high after the flood.
For this reason, we are
making our game accordingly.
Do you have another intention..
...with this invitation?
Those ruling with blood
are to be treated with blood.
Don't be worrying at all.
e make all of our moves to destroy Tajeddin Noyan.
You’ll see when you come to the yard.
Your heart will be at ease then.
Tell me. Your people are on the way.
Where will you settle in?
Wherever we can be the
farthest away from Mongolians.
It will take a long time for us to
heal our wounds, Osman Bey.
-We'll go south.
-Well...
Will you leave us alone?
-No.
I will make my people settle in.
And then I will come back for vengeance.
I want to host..
...your people and alps in my lands. Stay here.
We would be a burden for you, Osman Bey.
And Tajeddin Noyan's wrath would be on you.
Maybe that's what I want.
Maybe I want to...
...drive him mad with fury, reveal
the animal inside him and choke him.
You can't leave me alone in such a situation.
You'll be with us. We will protect Yenisehir.
And we will see the end together.
Well... What can I say, Osman Bey?
The destiny says the last words.
May Allah help us.
-Thank you.
I will make you feel better.
You are my only confidant.
I can't talk to anyone else.
We are alps',,after all. Should
alps complain about hard duties?
e are alps, after all. Should
They shouldn't.
They shouldn't talk but you understand me.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
-Nothing. I was talking about
a problem with my companion.
Judging by how it seems,
it seems like a big problem.
I am ashamed of calling it a problem.
A duty... It is a big duty, but...
...do you know who I am?
Ghazi Alp, the son of Cerkutay, who was a spy.
Everyone in this marketplace
calls me "the son of a spy".
But I am Osman Bey's Alp.
No burden is too heavy for me. I can
fight with a sword and keep a secret.
It's obvious. You are a valiant warrior.
You are saying that you can keep a secret, huh?
Osman Bey is an important Bey
who fights on the way of Allah.
He follows the sunnah of the Messenger of Allah
(PBUH).
Did you know?
Our Efendi also had friends at your age.
Really?
-Really, yes.
The first Muslim child, the Shah
of honest men, Hadhrat Ali (RA).
I know him! Yes I do! He laid in
the Rasullullah's (PBUH) bed...
...and played a game against polytheists.
-Oh Praise be!
There was someone else. Anas ibn Malik.
Do you also know him?
Anas ibn Malik was an orphan.
In the hejira of our Prophet to Medina...
...his mother gave him to
the service of our Prophet.
He was 8 years old back then and he never
left his side until our Prophet's passing.
He was present in all battles. He
participated in the Battle of Badr...
...when he was only 12 years old.
But more importantly...
...Anas ibn Malik was the
confidant of our Prophet.
A child confidant.
Our Prophet would give
him his secrets and duties...
...and he never worried about them...
...because he knew that Anas ibn Malik...
...would always keep his secrets.
He was young..
...but his imaan was great.
No matter what happened, he
wouldn't tell anyone his secret...
...not even his mother. Even if
our Prophet's wives asked him...
...he wouldn't tell them. He wouldn't tell anyone.
Now you're saying that...
...you can keep Osman Bey's secret.
You are really lucky... you have...
...taken on an important duty for Osman
Bey's blessed way. But now you know that...
...you are not alone.
There were brave children like you in the past.
They were servants of Islam.
You are one of them.
-Am I really one of them?
-Yes.
And you... Dervish Efendi, who are you?
They call me Taptuk's Yunus.
-Taptuk’s Yunus?
Shahzades are always telling me your words’
Are you really Yunus Emre?
My companion is injured...
I treated its wound but...
..if you allow me, I want to entrust it to you.
Alaeddin Bey...
-Gonca Hatun.
Alps.
They said you went to Kutahya.
My father and my mother left. I am
at the marketplace with my brother.
Is that so?
It is forbidden for
Germiyanoglu to enter Yenisehir.
-What are you doing here?
-I am not here for a visit. I have things to say.
Tell me.
Alaeddin Bey. Tajeddin Noyan
...came to frontiers marketplace
last night. He talked to my brother.
I am afraid my brother is going to
make a mistake and unite with him.
What fitna are you trying to cause again?
Tell me... How am I going
to believe your words, huh?
I made one mistake. And I
am paying its price, Alaeddin.
I came here and put my life at
risk, against my brother's will.
I know that he is going to kill me.
You will bring Alaeddin's head to me. I
will make him experience the worst pain.
I will take his son from
him. Alaca will handle this.
I came.
...because I don’t want my
family to make another mistake.
I said what I had to say.
Now I am not responsible for that.
You can believe it or not.
Good.
I believe you.
Now go back to your marketplace.
-Alaeddin!
-Gonca!
Gonca!
-Tell me, Mehmet Bey.
Tajeddin Noyan came to see me.
He said "I will cut your head
off if you unite with Osman."
And..
...why are you telling me this?
I am obeying my father's orders.
He ordered me and said "Keep your
relationship good with Osman Bey."
Tajeddin Noyan will not
only cause problems for you...
...but also for me.
I wanted you to know that
and take your steps accordingly.
My Bey. Mehmet and Tajeddin Noyan met.
It seems they are after an alliance.
Oh Mehmet...
No one allies with Tajeddin Noyan.
He only looks for a dog to use for himself.
Go to the Frontier Marketplace.
Tajeddin Noyan will come
here. Don't let him see you here.
However, if he wants something from you..
-..inform me about it.
-Do not worry, Osman Bey.
I'll have my leave now.
He made his people just like himself.
The heads of these strongheads,
won't leave on their bodies for long.
Wrong. On the contrary..
..these are the hardest ones to crush.
Come on.
These people believe in their leader so much..
..that you can not crush them
before crushing their belief.
Pity, they became blind.
However, I will show them the truth.
Come on!
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
So, Osman Bey..
..I hope you will give the good news.
Have you decided yet?
-I decided long ago.
I am curiously waiting for
your response. However..
..I have information for you.
Princess Maria, whom you kept
away from me, is in my hands.
I know.
However, you should hear this as well.
I will never bow down to you.
I will never pay any tax to you.
And if you want a single alp from me..
..you will never get it. Know this well.
You are making a mistake, Osman Bey.
Think about what will happen.
You are threatening the lives of..
..Gunduz Bey and Ayca
Hatun, whom you care so much.
I don't threaten anyone's life.
Bring them!
Do you think you are the only one playing tricks?
We got away from your
hands for now, Tajeddin Noyan.
However, we will stand against you soon.
You impressed me, Osman Bey.
However, my patience has ran out.
Know this well.
If war will start..
..this will not be good for you at all.
e are not afraid of death.
We live with death.
Bring the Karacelasun dog
You will hold this dog's leash.
Since you put him among us to play your tricks..
..killing this dog does not fit me.
Osman, for the final time..
Shut it!
Keep that worm tongue of yours to yourself!
You oppressed the innocent.
You raised your hand to them!
Didn't you have no shame
when you laid down for sajdah?
Which book was it written what you did?
My name is Osman Bey.
I will never bow down to you!
If war is what you want, there
is the field, there are the soldiers.
Do not fall back.
-Osman.
I will make you pay for this.
From now on, you won't be able to breathe freely.
I won't stop until every
single person in this city dies.
I will make you
live in hell, Osman!
Threats are for jackals. Don't fall back!
Beys! Alps!
The great war has started!
Now, ride your horses to the north..
..to the east, to the west and to the south!
Send word to Turk tribes and beys!
Tell them, the war of existence has started!
The era of peace is over!
From now on, it’s time to rise up!
-Allah is the greatest!
Oh Allah
Visit turkision.com for more!